Guide to the Kensinger Jones Papers, 1934-2001 and undated RL.00648
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Writings and Speeches, 1944-2001 and undated, bulk 1955-1972
  - Speeches, 1955-1974 and undated
    - 1968
      - Direct Mail to Whom? Direct Mail Club of Detroit, Mar. 7 (Box 63)
      - Cancelled by Jones, 1967 Nov. 21 Midwest Gas Association, Apr. (Box 63)
      - Direct Mail to Whom? Sales and Marketing Executive Club of Jackson, Inc. Hayes Motor Hotel, Jackson, Mich., May 27 (Box 63)
    - 1969
      - Nobody Makes an Ad, re Oldsmobile, 1969 catalog, Fourth Annual Advertising Agency Day, Alpha Delta Sigma, National Professional Advertising Fraternity, Leo Burnett Chapter. Ferris State College, Big Rapids, Mich., Apr. 16 (Box 63)
      - Nobody Makes an Ad. [No text of speech] Advertising course by AAAA at Wayne State University McGregor Auditorium, Detroit. Correspondence from students in course, May 1 (Box 63)
      - "Talk, ten minutes" initiation banquet, honorary membership in Alpha Delta Sigma, Leo Burnett chapter, Ferris State College, Big Rapids, Mich. memos, Aug. 23 (Box 64)
      - Nobody Makes an Ad: Alpha Kappa Psi, business fraternity, University of Michigan-Dearborn, Sept. 17 (Box 64)
      - Involvement - It's Wonderful: Parents without Partners Gross Pointe Chapter, Gross Pointe War Memorial, Gross Pointe Farms, Mich., Sept. 26 (Box 64)
      - [Two speeches at AAAA Central Region - Joint Meeting with Adcraft Club of Detroit] J.E. O'Toole: What We Know about Creative Management... and E.N. Cole: Who and Where Is the Customer?, Nov.6-7 (Box 64)
      - Who and Where is the Customer? Upstairs in the Big, Corner Office speech by Robert S. Marker, [advertising professional] The Adcraft Club of Detroit (in folder with 1969, Nov.6-7 [Two speeches.. .), Dec. 5 (Box 64)
    - 1970
      - Bowlers, Broilers, and Bags or Sell It Like It Is. (5th Annual) Sales Promotion Executives Association, Detroit re (advertising for H. Salt. Fish and Chips restaurants), Mar. 13 (Box 64)
      - Advertising - A Very Involved Business: AAAA Task Force program at Adrian College, Mich. (speech on creativity either Nobody Makes An Ad or Bowler, Boilers... ) signed letter from Leo Burnett, Apr.24 (Box 64)
      - Be Prepared, Help Other People At All Times - and Skills to Carry Them Out, Boy Scouts, Eagle Court of Honor First United Methodist Church, Birmingham, Mich., May 20 (Box 64)
    - 1972
      - Please Don't Pick the Flowers, Harrisburg Advertising Club. Includes parody of poem The Charge of the Light Brigade, Feb. 16 (Box 64)
      - Don't Wait for George to do It: speech by L. S. Matthews, President, Leo Burnett Company, Inc. Off-the-Street Club - 72nd Annual Meeting, Chicago, Jun. 14 (Box 64)
      - The Experts on the Fourteenth Floor or There Are People Besides Lawyers Who Care About the Truth. AAAA, Central Region, Chicago, Oct. 20 (Box 64)
    - 1973
      - General Outline for Creative Presentations in South-East Asia, May 7 (Box 64)
      - The Strange and Wonderful World of a Regional Creative Director: International Advertising Association, Sydney, Australia, Jun. 28 (Box 64)
    - 1974
      - Speech to the Advertisers' Association [Singapore], May 24 (Box 64)
    - Undated
      - Untitled speech for Public Service Communications Council, Chicago [ca. 1970s] (Box 64)
      - Untitled presentation about execution of advertising strategies [undated] (Box 64)
  - Published Articles, 1959-1972
    Arranged chronologically, the Published Articles Subseries contains the text and correspondence for articles to be published in regional and national advertising publications. At the end are articles submitted to Advertising Age. A chronological listing is in a folder at the beginning of the series.
    - 1959 (Box 65)
      - Symbology - Fourth Communications Conference of Art Directors Club of N.Y., Apr. 1-2 [titled folder, empty] (Box 65)
    - 1963
      - Detroit is a Great Idea Town, Radio station WDET - FM Detroit, Jun. 10 (Box 65)
      - The Four I's - A Working Philosophy for Campbell-Ewald, Booklet for internal agency distribution (Box 65)
      - The 'Copy Chief' Computer submitted to Printers' Ink along with The Copywriter, comments, Jones's reply to their questionnaire about copywriter for a special issue, Sept. (Box 65)
      - What is the Commercial Co-Efficient for Success, Sponsor Magazine, Sept. 30, p. 12 (Box 65)
    - 1964
      - Agency's Role in Packaging comments Packaging Design Magazine, May/Jun. [correspondence only] (Box 65)
      - Memo to Creative People, Madison Avenue, Jun., pp. 38-40, 46,59 (Box 65)
      - Memo to Creative People, Dimension 15, College of Art and Architecture, University of Michigan, Spring, pp. 52-61 (Box 65)
      - The World's Greatest Institutional Advertisement (re World's Fair, 1964), printed by World's Fair, Aug. (Box 65)
      - "Comments," SAM Magazine (Serving Advertising in the Midwest), Nov. 27, pp. 17 (Box 65)
    - 1966
      - The Important Extra submitted to the 33rd annual competition of the Institute of Outdoor Advertising, Jan. (Box 65)
    - 1967
      - Understanding McLuhan, OPT Magazine, Fall, pp. 16-18 (Box 65)
    - 1968
      - Ad Business 'Contributes to Confusion, Flaunts Prejudice' in United Negro College Fund Ad [letter to the Editor] Advertising Age, Mar. 18 re advertisement in 1968 Mar. 4 issue (Box 65)
    - Articles submitted to Advertising Age:
      - Here Come the Judge: How Fair Are Ad Competitions? Advertising Age, July 29 1968, p. 52; includes correspondence, 1968 May (Box 65)
      - Techniques, Talent and TV (not published), 1968 Jun. (Box 65)
      - Detroit-Crucible for Creativity (rewritten version) SAM Magazine, 1969 Mar. 27 (Box 65)
      - Detroit-Crucible for Creativity, Torchlight: Annual Roster and Buyer's Guide, Cleveland Advertising Club, 1969 Oct., 2 folders (Box 65)
      - The Charge of the Light Brigade (After review with the FTC lawyers): typescripts and correspondence re publication in Advertising Age and HLG newsletter, 1971 Oct. (Box 65)
      - The Executive Reel in Journal of Advertising, v.1 no.1, 1972. Typescript, correspondence, issues of journal, news clippings, 1972 May (Box 65)
  - Other Writings, St. Louis, 1944-1951 and undated
    Arranged alphabetically by title, this subseries primarily includes writing from Jones's early career as a freelance writer in St. Louis.
    - All Americans - script, flipcards, and photographs for TV program for KSD-TV, St. Louis, presented as a salute to Brotherhood Week by the National Council of Christians and Jews, ca. 1950-1951 (Box 66)
    - Audition Scripts - Shave and Shoeshine for Step'n Fetch it show; Top of the Morning, [ca. 1940s] (Box 66)
    - Biographical Data on E.M. Statler" - hotel founder and his St. Louis hotel, Inside Inn, built for Louisiana Purchase Exposition in St. Louis, ca. 1904 (Box 66)
    - Boy Scouts of America, St. Louis Council - Scripts for Boy Scout Circus, 1945-1951 (Box 66)
    - Community Organizations, St. Louis, community chest, Ad Club, Rotary Club, and others, ca. 1950-1952 (Box 66)
    - Copy for Radio Show and commercials, 1950 and undated (Box 66)
    - Forests for the Future ... in Barry County, Michigan, brochure [undated] (Box 66)
    - Here's Housing television script for ground breaking ceremony for public housing in St. Louis Including 1955 correspondence re expenses, 1952 (Box 66)
    - Human Rights Day Celebration - Keil Opera House, St. Louis, 1951 Dec. 10 (Box 66)
    - Lammert Furniture Company, St. Louis - Proposal, statement and notes for 90th anniversary celebrations, [ca. 1950-1951] (Box 66)
    - Land We Live In - script and other information, 1946-1950 and undated (Box 66)
    - Make It Live - A presentation of the Queen's workshop of the Air, [1950s] (Box 66)
    - Miscellaneous World War II writings, 1945-1946, 1982 (Box 66)
    - Passport to Yesterday- an entertainment show about the history of St. Louis for the 36th Annual Meeting of Kiwanis International in St. Louis. [no script] contact and press coverage, 1951 (Box 66)
    - Print Brochures and catalogs - examples of copy written by Ken Jones, including pay check stubs for early writing, ca. 1939-1951 and undated (Box 67)
    - Print Brochures - designed and written by Ken Jones as a freelancer, 1980-1990s (Box 67)
    - Radio scripts for various programs in St. Louis, 1946 and undated (Box 67)
    - Radio Scripts for radio programs - some for KMOX, including four scripts for the Pet Milk Show, 1947, 1949, and undated (Box 67)
    - Radio Scripts for anniversary programs for Monsanto, [1940s] (Box 67)
    - Speech - re history of St. Louis; correspondence re advertising; copy for brochure for Missouri Pacific Railroad, 1940, 1949, and undated (Box 67)
    - Two Gentlemen of Broadway - a musical revue, new clipping and printed notice, 1949; [no script] Not so long ago - a night club show, 1949; What's Happened to the Bands for Griff Williams Band [undated] (Box 67)
    - Union Electric - Scripts for radio programs commercials, and programs for anniversary and other group meetings, 1949-1952 and undated, 2 folders (Box 67)
    - Your Missouri - The Story of Missouri University - film scripts for Hard castle Films, n.d (Box 67)
  - Other Writings, 1960-2001 and undated
    This subseries includes published and unpublished literary and autobiographical writing, published articles and books about Jones's advertising career and experiences in World War II, miscellaneous speeches and talks, and other short pieces such as reviews and brochures for various groups. Arranged alphabetically by title.
    - The Ballad of Sam Hildebrand, 1967 (reprinted from 1946) (Box 68)
    - Baltimore: the Most Unexpected Township, 2001 (Box 68)
    - Cable Advertising: New Ways to New Business, by Kensinger Jones, Thomas F. Baldwin, and Martin P. Block, 1986 (Box 68)
    - A Call From The Country, by Kensinger Jones and Alice Guseman Jones, 1989 (Box 68)
    - Career Awareness, speech to elementary school about advertising careers [undated] (Box 68)
    - Celebrity Lecture Series Enjoys Major Success, MSU Alumni Magazine, Winter 1995 (Box 68)
    - Charlton Park Veteran's Picnic speech, July 4, 2001 (Box 68)
    - Christmas, Recollected, 1999 (Box 68)
    - Corvair Lives! The Adcrafter, ca. 1995 (Box 68)
    - Corvair--TV Star of the 60s, speech to Corvair Convention, 1994 July 29 (Box 68)
    - Drasko Vidic Speech, American Independent Party Convention, 1970 (Box 68)
    - Dream Homes With Their Feet on the Ground, 1969 (Box 68)
    - Educational Adventure: Twelve Days in China, The Adcrafter, ca. 1990 (Box 68)
    - Hometown, poem, 1981 (Box 68)
    - Letter, Automobile, 1988 Feb. (Box 68)
    - Letter, Michigan History Magazine, 1991 Nov.-Dec. (reprinted from Dec. 8, 1941 (Box 68)
    - Love Poems of a Businessman, by Kensinger Jones with editing and notes by Alice Guseman Jones, 1997 (Box 68)
    - Memo to: Creative People, Madison Avenue, [ca. 1960-1967] (Box 69)
    - Miscellaneous Poems, 1966 (Box 69)
    - unspecified (Box 69)
    - The Most Terrifying Thing in the World, poem, [undated] (Box 69)
    - North to Alaska and The Alcan, Michigan History Magazine, 1992 Sept.-Oct. (Box 69)
    - Off the Street Club speech, written for Len Matthews, 1973 (Box 69)
    - Operation Kensinger, Michigan History, 1996 Mar.-Apr. (Box 69)
    - Pierce Cedar Creek Institute brochure, [ca. 2001] (Box 69)
    - Pinnacle, unpublished novel [undated], 2 folders (Box 69)
    - The Player, various reviews and flyers, 1960-1965 (Box 69)
    - Programs, Packards, and Pinnacles, The Adcrafter, ca. 1993 (Box 69)
    - Sure, Dad, autobiographical short story, [ca. 1968] (Box 69)
    - Words, words, words, speech to B'nai B'rith, Mar. 27, 1974 (Box 69)
    - Write Away ..., unpublished autobiography [undated], 2 folders (Box 70)
    - Untitled speech about the "new wave of socially conscious advertising," [undated] (Box 70)
- Personal Files, 1934-2002 and undated
  The Personal Series includes materials about Jones's dedicated involvement in civic affairs with groups such as the Boy Scouts and the World Relief Fund; writings about his service in Alaska during WWII; personal correspondence; and other miscellaneous documents. Of particular note are the materials by and about Leo Burnett and the Leo Burnett Advertising Agency. Arranged alphabetically by category of material.
  - Career (Box 71)
    - Resume, 1957-1982 (Box 71)
    - Correspondence with Knox Reeves Advertising about job offers, 1960, 1968 (Box 71)
    - Article--Thank You, John W. Hartman, Adcrafter Roster, 2002 (Box 71)
    - Reviews of Jones's Cable Advertising: New Ways to New Business, 1986 (Box 71)
    - Memo to Traver and Associates, client, 1991 Jun. 19 (Box 71)
    - Review of Jones's and Alice Guseman Jones's A Call from the Country, from Hard Roe to Hoe: Reviews from Rural America, 1993 (Box 71)
    - Excerpt on Jones from unidentified book on advertising [undated] (Box 71)
  - Correspondence
    - Education, community activities and radio writing, 1934-1952 and undated (Box 71)
    - Family and colleagues, 1955-1957 and undated (Box 71)
    - Ralph Olmstead, 1956-1989 (Box 71)
    - Miscellaneous personal, 1961-1967 (Box 71)
    - Michigan elected officials regarding federal income tax surcharge, 1968 (Box 71)
    - U.S. Information Agency, 1968-1969 (Box 71)
    - Miscellaneous personal, 1970 (Box 71)
    - Letters of thanks from students, 1975 (Box 71)
    - Miscellaneous personal, 1974-1994 and undated (Box 71)
  - Leo Burnett materials
    - Burnett History--An Interview with Ken Jones, transcript, 1972 Feb. 22, conducted by Jack O'Kieffe (Box 71)
    - The Clash of New Marketing Insights with Old Mythologies, speech by Burnett, "Chicago Marketing Man of the Year" Award Dinner, 1966 Feb. 11 (Box 72)
    - Correspondence to, from, and about Burnett, 1952-1994 and undated, 2 folders (Box 72)
    - Photographs of colleagues, ca. 1950s (Box 72)
    - Printed materials about Burnett and company, 1956-1992 and undated (Box 72)
    - Printed materials about Burnett's death, 1971 (Box 72)
    - Printed materials from Advertising Age, 1967-1995 and undated (Box 72)
  - Organizations
    - Barry County, Mich. civic activities, 1981-1999 (Box 72)
    - Boy Scouts of America, 1981-1985, Folders 1-3 of 4 (Box 72)
    - Boy Scouts of America, 1981-1985, Folder 4 of 4 (Box 73)
    - Citizens for LeMay Committee, 1967 (Box 73)
    - McCarthy for President, 1968 (Box 73)
    - Michigan Office of Emergency Planning, 1961-1963, 3 folders (Box 73)
    - World Medical Relief, Inc., 1961-1992, Folders 1-3 of 5 (Box 73)
    - World Medical Relief, Inc., 1961-1992, Folders 4-5 of 5 (Box 74)
    - Various club memberships, 1967-1971 (Box 74)
  - Printed Material
    - Larry Claypool, A Historical Look at Corvair TV Advertising, Corsa Communique, 1994 Sept. (Box 74)
    - Rome Cowgill, Fundamentals of Writing for Radio, 1949 (Box 74)
    - Alice M. [Guseman] Jones, The History of An Advertising Agency Library, Master's thesis, 1967 (Box 74)
    - Miscellaneous clippings, 1965-1986 and undated (Box 74)
    - Wilfrid A. Peterson, miscellaneous publications (Box 74)
    - Printed material about The Land We Live In, 1947 (Box 74)
- Audiovisual Materials, 1959-1996 and undated
  This series is arranged by media format subseries: 35mm slides, videotapes, audiotapes, and 16mm films that document commercials, speeches, and seminars and often augment print materials elsewhere in the collection. Live action film commercials for Chevrolet advertising on television shows from 1957-1967, such as The Dinah Shore Show, Bonanza, and Bewitched, were typically produced in Hollywood or Europe. In 1959 and 1960, two films won international awards - American in Paris and Magic Ride. A Child of My Own, is a film created for the Singapore Tourist Promotion Board in 1974-1975. Other films, including Creativity (renamed The Horse and Fiddle), Truth and Consequences: Form and Function in Advertising, The Importance of Being Interesting, and The Minstrel Principle, originated as seminar speeches with slide illustrations and were later produced as films. Whatever Happened to Mrs. Momiyama, a speech to students, was developed by the Advertising Association of America into a filmstrip and film for secondary schools about advertising, American business, and the Japanese economy after WWII.
  - 35mm slides, 1968-1988 and undated
    Arranged alphabetically by title.
    - Audette Cadillac and other clients, ca. 1979, 20 slides (Box 75)
    - Automotive clients, unspecified, undated, 33 slides (Box 75)
    - Direct Mail to Whom? Direct Mail Club of Detroit, 1968 Mar. 7; and Sales and Marketing Club of Jackson, Mich., 1968 May 27, 31 slides (Box 75)
    - Ex-Cell-O: Basic Balance Building, undated, 28 slides (Box 75)
    - Ford Marketing Institute, ca. 1978, 86 slides (Box 75)
    - The Minstrel Principle, Toledo Advertising Club, 1967 Nov. 15, 72 slides (Box 75)
    - Otto Oldsmobile, undated, 28 slides (Box 75)
    - U.S.-China Exchange Program in Advertising, 1988, 80 slides (Box 75)
    - Who Cares About the Truth? [Sydney, Australia? ca. 1973], 63 slides (Box 75)
    - Unidentified, five numbered incomplete sequences, undated, 92 slides (Box 75)
    - Unidentified and unnumbered slides, undated, 60 slides (Box 76)
    - Scripts and logs for various 16mm films, videotapes, and audiotapes, 3 folders (Box 76)
  - Videotapes, 1959-1996 and undated
    Arranged in three formats--U-matic videocassette, VHS videocassette, and 2" video reel--and then alphabetically by title within each format.
    - U-matic videocassettes (Box 77)
      - 1. Barry County, Mich. three cuts of interview with Jones, County Grants Coordinator, ca. 1970s (3/4" U-matic UCA-30 videocassette) (Box 77)
      - 2. Bureau of Newspaper Advertising. Interview with Jones and other creative directors from Detroit, 1965 (3/4" U-matic UCA-10S videocassette) (Box 77)
      - 3. Campbell-Ewald farewell party, 1968, and unspecified film footage transferred to videotape for MSU Adv 441 in 1984 (3/4" U-matic UCA-30 videocassette) (Box 77)
      - 4. Community National Bank commercial for Wilding Advertising, 1979 (3/4" U-matic UCA-5 videocassette) (Box 77)
      - 5. Demo tape for Wilding Advertising. Three commercials: Chartered Bank, Singapore, 1974; Detroit Symphony, 1976; and Detroit Institute of the Arts, 1976. (3/4" U-matic UCA-5 videocassette) (Box 77)
    - VHS Videocassettes
      - 6. Advertising 441 Lecture: Magic Ride, 1961; and American in Paris, 1959 (1/2" VHS videocassette) (Box 77)
      - 7. America on Wheels. PBS television documentary with Jones's participation. Partial log, June 17, 1996 (1/2" VHS videocassette) (Box 77)
      - 8. College of Communication Arts and Sciences, The Advancing Frontier, 1988 (1/2" VHS videocassette) (Box 78)
      - 9. Corvair convention. Includes 36 commercials and video exhibits, 1994 (1/2" VHS videocassette) (Box 78)
      - 10. Florida. For Adv 441 and Campbell-Ewald Collegiate competition, [198?] (1/2" VHS videocassette) (Box 78)
      - 11. Michigan. For Adv 441 and Campbell-Ewald Collegiate competition, [198?] (1/2" VHS videocassette) (Box 78)
      - 12. MSU Instructional Tape. Four cuts: Magic Ride, American in Paris, Bill Walker, jingle writer, guest lecture, and Eddie Birnbryer and daughter Annie, copywriters, guest lecture, ca. 1986 (1/2" VHS videocassette) (Box 78)
      - 13. Restaurant Seminar. Includes commercials from Leo Burnett and Campbell-Ewald, [undated] (1/2" VHS videocassette) (Box 78)
      - 14. Some Advertising Ideas in Storyboard Form. 24 cuts; Log, 1989 (1/2" VHS videocassette) (Box 78)
      - 15. Taiwanese commercials for seminar. Includes paper notes, 1987 (1/2" VHS videocassette) (Box 78)
      - 16. The Time Machine - Drive for the American Dream. Television documentary with Jones's participation; includes Chevrolet commercials. Includes partial log, 1993 (1/2" VHS videocassette) (Box 78)
    - Videotape reels
      - 17. Chevrolet, American in Paris. Cannes Festival award winning commercial, 1959 (2" videotape reel) (Box 78)
      - 18. Chevrolet, Magic Ride. Cannes Festival award winning commercial, 1961 (2" videotape reel) (Box 78)
  - Audiotapes, 1964-1995 and undated
    Arranged in two formats--audiocassttes and reel-to-reel tapes--and then alphabetically by title within each format.
    - 1. Audette Cadillac, thirteen sixty-second spots, 1/4" audiocassette, 1979 (Box 79 (Cassettes))
    - 2. Auto Dealer Award Winning Commercials, 1/4" audiocassette, 1978 (Box 79 (Cassettes))
    - 3. Burnett Breakfast: Music, Music, Music, 1/4" audiocassette, [undated] (Box 79 (Cassettes))
    - 4. Burnett Door speech and experimental unused radio tracks for Green Giant and Pabst Blue Ribbon Beer, 1/4" audiocassette, [undated] (Box 79 (Cassettes))
    - 5. Chevrolet commercials, 1/4" audiocassette, 1967 (Box 79 (Cassettes))
    - 6. Clio Award Winners, 1/4" audiocassette, 1988 (Box 79 (Cassettes))
    - 7. Clio Award Winners, 1/4" audiocassette, 1988-1989 (Box 79 (Cassettes))
    - 8. Copy Workshop Radio, Instruction Tape, 1/4" audiocassette with partial log, [undated] (Box 79 (Cassettes))
    - 9. Greatest Radio Commercials, 1930-1940s, 1/4" audiocassette, [undated] (Box 79 (Cassettes))
    - 10. Larke Chevrolet and McDonald's, Adv 417, 1/4" audio cassette, 1995 (Box 79 (Cassettes))
    - 11. The Lone Ranger, 1/4" audiocassette, [undated] (Box 79 (Cassettes))
    - 12. Mercury Awards, 1/4" audiocassette, 1994 (Box 79 (Cassettes))
    - 13. Michigan State University, sixty-second promos from Adv 321, 1994, Fall, 1/4" audiocassette, 1994 (Box 79 (Cassettes))
    - 14. New Car Dealers, twenty spots including 1971 Freeberg spot, 1/4" audiocassette, ca. 1978-1979. (Box 79 (Cassettes))
    - 15. Plummet Mall, 1/4" audiocassette, ca. 1984 (Box 79 (Cassettes))
    - 16. Radio's Top 40 for 1991, Mercury Awards, 1/4" audiocassette, 1992 (Box 79 (Cassettes))
    - 17. Steve Coppola Radio Resume, 1/4" audiocassette, ca. 1985-1989 (Box 79 (Cassettes))
    - 18. 20 of the World's Best Ads of 1967, 1/4" audiocassette, 1967 (Box 79 (Cassettes))
    - 19. Chevrolet commercial, ca. 1964; Camaro - Pete Estes, ca. 1964 (Box 80 (Reel-to-reel))
    - 20. Chevrolet theme music; Bewitched; and Bonanza generic themes [undated] (Box 80 (Reel-to-reel))
    - 21. Community National Bank, Community Touchdown Fight Song, for Wilding Agency, 1979 Sept. 5 (Box 80 (Reel-to-reel))
    - 22. 1st in Your Life, with acc. letter, Artie Fields Productions Detroit, Mich., ca. 1960s (Box 80 (Reel-to-reel))
    - 23. In My Merry Olds, Columbia Gramophone [undated] (Box 80 (Reel-to-reel))
    - 24. The Land We Live In: Sad Man's Music, copy of 1950s radio show (Box 80 (Reel-to-reel))
    - 25. Leo Rosten speech, AAAA, 1965 Apr. 24 (Box 80 (Reel-to-reel))
    - 26. The Minstrel Principle, speech by Jones, AAAA East Central Meeting, Pittsburgh, Pa., [undated] (Box 80 (Reel-to-reel))
    - 27. Thirteen commercials with annotated log, Bill Walker Productions, N. Riverside, Ill., [undated] (Box 80 (Reel-to-reel))
    - 28. Who Cares about the Truth, speech by Jones in Sydney, Australia (see text and slides), ca. 1973 (Box 80 (Reel-to-reel))
    - 29. Who Cares about the Truth ("extra tape" ) (Box 80 (Reel-to-reel))
  - 16mm films, 1962-1980 and undated
    Arranged alphabetically by title. Some titles assigned during processing.
    - 1. Australia and New Zealand commercials, including log, 1973-1974 (Box 81)
    - 2. Bureau of Newspaper Advertising, 1971 (Box 81)
    - 3. Burnett Malaysia, seven commercials including log, ca. 1973-1976 (Box 82)
    - 4. Campbell-Ewald Farewell, 1968 (Box 82)
    - 5. [Campbell head, untitled, undated] (Box 82)
    - 6. Child of My Own, Petersen Company, Hollywood, Calif., 1974-1976 (Box 82)